<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Active Ideas Comment RSS Feed</title>
    <link>http://ideas.active.com</link>
    <description>Comments on awesome ideas for Active</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 13:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#43</link>
      <description>good question.  no next steps being taken yet.  Chuck was going to drive it but with recent changes we've lost him as a champion.  Should know who the new champion is in a few weeks.</description>
      <author>Jeremy Thomas</author>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 13:26:45 -0800</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#42</link>
      <description>Are next steps being taken?  Who is now driving this?</description>
      <author>Marc Kozai</author>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 14:54:49 -0800</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monetize Holiday Gift Guide</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/46#41</link>
      <description>Mike, how do these referral programs work?  And do you envision them being self-service?</description>
      <author>Jeremy Thomas</author>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2008 13:24:49 -0800</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings for customer reviews...</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/42#40</link>
      <description>Yep, planing on a release on 3 December, 2008.</description>
      <author>Jeremy Thomas</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:42:11 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#39</link>
      <description>Ultimately unless the client pays to have the ads removed from their page the ads will be there.  So the key here would be to position this as an opportunity to:

a)       Increase continuity between event sponsors and advertising on page (when applicable)

b)       Ensure that conflicting advertisers do not display on the page.
</description>
      <author>Marc Kozai</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:37:46 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#38</link>
      <description>The estimation was VERY loosely based on approximate numbers, was done in 5 min and was not $500k.  Here was the thought process.
 
50% of the traffic on Active.com comes from event detail pages.
Of this 50% about 60% comes from endurance related pages.
Conclusion: So about 30% of our traffic comes from endurance event detail pages.
 
Endurance pages sell for about 50% higher rate than ROS pages.
Endurance is always in high demand and can easily sell out
Active.com (only) drives about $1-2 million in revenue per year
Conclusion: We could drive 50% more revenue to 30% of our traffic.
 
Bottom line: 30% of our revenue is $300-600k and a 50% increase gives you a $150-300k lift in revenue.
 
I just looked at our 2009 inventory forecast.  We are forecasting about 60 million impressions for next year to event details.  If we again assume 60% of that is endurance traffic we are left with 36 million.  If you assume we sell endurance inventory for an extra $5 CPM.  The lift becomes $180k.  Of course assuming 100% sell thru.
 
There are definitely other factors but this is just a quick analysis. </description>
      <author>Marc Kozai</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:37:34 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#37</link>
      <description>Thanks for the idea.  

Sponsors would not have the opportunity to approve certain events.  

Happy to flush out idea further with Marc to have a better understanding of what he is envisioning.
</description>
      <author>Ingrid Sanders</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#36</link>
      <description>Would Sponsors have the opportunity to approve is selected by an ED?  There might be some events certain sponsors would rather not be affiliated with.</description>
      <author>Jason Aloia</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:36:02 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective ad display on Event Details pages</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/45#35</link>
      <description>Jeremy indicated he and Marc discussed a proposed solution to refereeing ED pages for endurance to create more inventory opportunities.

 

High Level

-         Active provides a list of sponsors that our clients can designate as sponsors of their event during the set up process

-         The sponsor list is automatically managed against a list maintained by Active’s ad operations

-         We know whether there is a conflict, no conflict, or how to manage the conflict by serving an approved ad

-         Marc indicated $500k inventory opportunity after initial analysis (not sure how the analysis was conducted and what exceptional circumstances or discounts were applied)

This is an interesting idea to pursue.  If there is truly opportunity here, it requires agreement w/ Eric this is rational and additional review of Marc’s analysis to ensure we have a shared understanding of the revenue creation opportunity.  If all signs point to yes, next step will be to build this into RC and Foundations.. can’t get in the queue too soon.

Ingrid – will you vet this with Eric as a viable solution?
Marc – can you provide an overview of your initial analysis?

Thank you.
</description>
      <author>Chuck Mitchell</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 15:35:45 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Blogs</title>
      <link>http://ideas.active.com/ideas/5#34</link>
      <description>Note we are doing this now: http://community.active.com/blogs/productdev</description>
      <author>Jeremy Thomas</author>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 12:12:44 -0700</pubDate>
    </item>
    <generator>Ruby's RSS::Maker</generator>
  </channel>
</rss>